

ANH DO

Nam



0962 507 172



27/09/2000

anhdh.cv@gmail.com

0

Tran Phu Street, Van Quan Ward, Ha Dong District, Ha Noi City

66

As an information technology student with a basic knowledge base, I want ajob with the position of building and developing web and mobile applications. Within one month, adapt to the job and working environment. Within 2 years, become project team leader to build and develop web andmobile applications.

EDUCATION

Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology (PTIT), Major:

Information Technology

08/2018 - Now

GPA: 3.32

WORK EXPERIENCE

Phuc Loc real estate company, Counselors

10/2018 - 03/2019

Taking care of customers on the phone.

Studying at PTIT, My projects

08/2018 - NOW

Some outstanding projects such as:

- The band
- Calculator
- My scoreboard
- Learn EV
- Distributed system
- · Chat online.

More information:

https://my-projects-anhdh.vercel.app

ACTIVITY

PTIT, International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) 03/01/2021 - 10/01/2021

SKILLS

Personal Skills:

- Office Information Technology
- Presentation
- Teamwork
- Lead team

Personal Projects (2018 - Now):

- HTML5, CSS/SCSS, JavaScript, jQuery Basic, Bootstrap 5.
- ReactJs, Redux, React Hook.
- C/C++ Basic, Java OOP, MySQL.
- Java EE, MCV model.
- Spring/Spring Boot, Django.
- Github.

HOBBIES

- Watch technology product review videos.
- Test technology products.

AWARD

2018 - Now: Scholarship for 5 semesters.

CERTIFICATE

2020: Samsung Algorithms and Applications.